Now, I'll step through an example of turning a high-level metric into
现在 我将通过一个示例 将一个高级指标转变为一个
a well-defined metric.
明确定义的指标
In lesson one,
在第一课中
we have chosen the high-level metric click-through probability.
我们选择了高级指标 点击概率
And we defined this as the number of unique users who clicked the button
将其定义为点击这个按钮的独立用户的数量
divided by the number of unique users who visited the home page.
除以访问主页的独立用户数量
Now, this is actually not a completely specified metric yet.
现在 这实际上不是一个完全定义的指标
And there are also some other possible definitions.
还有其他一些可用的定义
First, to use this definition,
首先 要使用这个定义
we need some way of determining whether two events are from the same user.
我们需要确定两个事件是否来自同一用户的方法
Let's say we use cookies.
比方说 我们使用 cookies
Next, if the same user or cookie visits the page once and
下一步 如果同一用户 或 cookie 访问这个网页一次
then comes back a week or two later, do we really only want to count that once?
然后 一两周之后再回来 我们真的会将访问量计算为一次吗？
Usually, you'll want to count those visits separately,
通常情况下 你会单独计算访问量
which means that you'll also need to choose a time period.
也就是说 你还需要选择一个时间段
Do you only count one page view per user each minute, hour, day, or what?
你是计算每个用户每分钟、每小时、还是每天的网页访问量吗？
So one fully specified definition would be that for each minute,
因此 如果针对每分钟而言 完全的定义是
you take the number of cookies that clicked during that minute divided by
将那分钟点击的 cookie 数量
the number of cookies that interacted with the page at all during that minute.
除以那分钟与网页互动的 cookie 数量
Now, this definition actually leads to a whole family of definitions
现在 这个定义会产生一系列定义
since you could choose any time interval here.
因为你在这里可能会选择任一时间段
Changing this time interval could give you a different answer.
更改这个时间段可能会给你一个不同的答案
For example, suppose your site only has one user who visits the site and clicks.
例如 假设只有一个用户访问并点击了你的网站
Then 5 minutes later, they reload the page but don't click.
5 分钟后 他们重新加载页面但没有点击
30 seconds after that, they reload again and do click this time.
30 秒之后 他们重新加载页面 并进行了点击
And then 12 hours later, they reload the page one last time and don't click.
12 小时后 他们最后一次重新加载 但没有点击
Assume that this user keeps the same cookie throughout this process.
假设这个用户在这个过程中保持同一 cookie
Now, if you group cookies by minute,
现在 如果你按照分钟将这些 cookies 分类
there are three separate groups where these two events are in the same group
这三组中有两组事件位于同一组
since they happened within a minute of each other.
因为 它们在一分钟之内发生
Since two of these groups resulted in a click, and the third did not,
由于这两组导致了一次点击 第三组则没有
the per-minute click-through probability is two-thirds.
因此 每分钟点击概率为三分之二
Similarly, if you group by hour, there are two groups,
同样 如果按照小时分组 有两组
one of which had a click, so the probability is one-half.
一组有一次点击 点击概率为二分之一
And if you group by day, everything goes in the same group and
如果按天分组 这些都分为同一组
the probability is one.
概率为一
An alternative definition would be to remove the idea of a unique user and
另一个备选定义去掉了独立用户的创意
instead to create a unique ID for each page view.
为每个网页浏览量创建一个唯一的 ID
And then when a user clicks,
当用户点击时
record the idea of the corresponding parent page view.
记录相应浏览母页的创意
Then you could define the click-through probability as the number of page views
然后将点击概率定义为产生点击的网页浏览量
that eventually result in a click divided by the number of page views.
除以网页浏览量
This data capture is usually easier than recording cookies and
数据捕获一般比 cookies 记录和
then later grouping by cookie.
cookie 分组更容易
Now, this definition also needs a time interval.
现在 这个定义还需要一个时间间隔
How long do you want to wait after each page view to see if it
浏览每个网页之后 你想等待多久
resulted in a click?
看看它是否会产生点击？
Once you pick a time interval,
选择一个时间段之后
you would count how many page views had a click within the specified time.
你就可以计算在指定的时间内有多少网页浏览量产生了点击
One way these two definitions could give different results is if the user
如果用户在规定的时间段内刷新网页
refreshes the page within the given time period.
这两个定义就会产生不同的结果
For example, suppose the user visits the page without clicking.
例如 假设用户访问了一个网页 但没有点击
Then 30 seconds later,
30 秒之后
they refreshed the page which generates another page view.
他们刷新了页面 产生新的网页浏览量
Finally, 1 second after the second page view, they click.
最后 在第二次页面浏览后 1 秒钟 他们进行了点击
Then, using definition one with a time interval of one minute so
然后 在一分钟的时间段内使用定义 1
that all these events are grouped together, there would be 1 cookie that
所有事件都被分为了一个组 那么就是点击的 1 个 cookie
clicked divided by 1 total cookie for a probability of 1.
除以 1 个 cookie 总量 概率是 1
But for definition two with the same time interval, only 1 page view resulted
定义 2 具有相同的时间段 总共 2 个网页浏览量
in a click over 2 total page views, so the probability would be one-half.
只有 1 个网页浏览量产生一次点击 因此 概率是二分之一
Finally, an even simpler definition would be to count the total number of
最后 一个更简单的定义是计算点击总量
clicks and divide by the total number of page views.
然后除以网页浏览总量
As you know, this would really be a click-through rate,
你知道 这实际上是点击率
rather than a click-through probability.
而不是点击概率
Which definition you use will depend on your product.
使用哪个定义取决于你的产品
Often, definitions one and two will be almost
一般情况下 如果你选择相同的相对较短的时间段
indistinguishable if you choose the same relatively short time interval.
定义 1 和 2 很难有区别
So you might want to go with definition two, since it's easier to compute.
因此 你可能更愿意选择定义 2 因为它更容易计算
Now, for each of the three definitions we just discussed,
现在 对于我们刚刚讨论的三个定义
the cookie-based probability, the page view-based probability, and
基于 cookie 的概率 基于网页浏览的概率和
the rate, consider whether it would be affected by the following problems.
比率 想想它们是否会受到以下问题的影响
You can find the complete definitions for
在讲师注释中有对这些指标的
these metrics in the instructor's notes.
完整定义
First, suppose you want your metric to be unaffected by the user double
首先 假设你想让你的指标
clicking.
不受用户双击的影响
That is, you want your metric to have the same value of
也就是说 你想让你的指标将同一时间点击两次
the user double clicks as if they single click.
等同于点击一次的值
Which of these metric definitions would work for this purpose?
哪个指标定义适用于此目的？
And second, when the user clicks the Back button, the browser may have cached
其次 当用户点击返回按钮 浏览器会缓存这个网页
the page, so another page view may or may not be generated.
因此 可能会也可能不会生成第二个网页浏览量
Which if these metrics would have the same value regardless of whether
当用户按返回按钮时 无论是否生成第二个网页浏览量
a second page view is generated when the user presses the Back button?
哪些指标具有相同的值？
Third, suppose you were worried that JavaScript may not be tracking clicks
第三 假设你担心 JavaScript 点击量可能
correctly.
未被正确跟踪
For example, it might send two clicks instead of one, or
例如 它可能发送两个点击量 而不是一个点击量
it might fail to record a click at all.
或可能根本没有记录点击量
Which metrics would have the same value regardless of whether
无论此类问题是否发生
problems such as this occurred?
哪些指标具有相同的值？
In each case, check the box for any metric that
针对每种情况 无论这些问题是否发生
would give the same value regardless of whether the problem occurred.
勾选具有相同值的指标
In each case, assume that all the relevant events occurs within the time
针对每种情况 假设所有相关事件在
interval for the probability metrics.
概率指标时间段内发生
So for example, if the time interval for the probabilities were five minutes,
例如 如果概率时间段是五分钟
assume that a double click happens within five minutes.
假设在这五分钟之内点击两次